Adelle King

Junior Fullstack Software Developer

adelle_king@outlook.com / 07703604622

Executive Summary

Driven and well rounded, offering a wealth of work experience gained within the NHS. Vast problem solving, change management, project management and leadership expertise.

My previous roles have encompassed working with, developing and enhancing tech to enhance productivity, improve work flow and introduce automation into the work place.

Education

 June 2023 - Present
 Code Institute
 Dublin, Ireland (Remote)

 Diploma in Fullstack Software Development (Accredited by the University West of Scotland)

Technical Skillset

Technologies	Databases	Frameworks	Version Control
HTML CSS Javascript Python Power Bl	MongoDB MySQL	Django jQuery Bootstrap	Git Github

Work Experience

May 2023 - Present NHS 111 National Service Advisor Remote

- Supporting callers who require medical assistance working through an algorithm to determine the best course of action to implement.
- Good telephone manner and the ability to use digital telephony systems.
- Ability to work effectively while dealing with high pressured calls, navigating the software safely to support the caller.

March 2023 - Present The Victory Academy Exam Invigilator Medway

- Supporting students in year 10 and 11 through their GCSE exams and their GCSE mock exams.
- Ensuring the JQC code of conduct is upheld, and all students receive a fair and safe exam experience.
- Ongoing training to enhance invigilating capabilities and embedding best practice into local policies.
- Working within a team alongside the teaching staff to provide a holistic environment.

March 2022-February 2023 Dartford and Gravesham Hospital Transformation and Improvement Lead Dartford.

- Project manager for transformation and improvement projects within the A&E and ward of the hospital.
- Projects undertaken included:
 - o The commissioning and building of a new modular ward with bespoke IT system to support the Endoscopy service.
 - Implementation of the cardiac virtual ward, enabling patients to have their care carried out at home rather than in a hospital setting.
 - Supporting the alcohol detox service to implement new ways of working with the community to reduce the number of
 admissions and improve the treatment given to patients. This includes a new system to be used by internal and external
 services.

January 2019 - February 2022 Medway Community Health Care Customer Care and Engagement Lead

- Strategic position, management of the complaints and engagement team.
- Worked alongside IT to implement a call handling system, which linked to Power BI.
- Worked alongside HR to develop a employee rostering system, including annual leave and sickness management.
- Worked with BI team to ensure our data was useful and easily accessible.

Certificates/Courses

Python Principles - Essential Python (40 hours)

Additional Information/Interests

- I am currently working on building my portfolio website.
- Regular engagement on Slack tech forum.
- I host a friendship group within my local area, designed to offer activities for people to join and meet others.

References available on request.